The Tufts Canon UP263
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Tufts Canon
2012 -- 2016
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Outbreath
UP263
0.55 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series.
Custodial History
While the first volume reference Fall 2011, it was not published until Spring 2012. The second volume was also published in Spring 2012.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of The Tufts Canon, a undergraduate literary journal published at least once per semester starting in the spring of 2012. The journal changed its name to Cannon in Summer 2016.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts Canon is a literary student organization that grew out of the former Outbreath literary group. It formed in 2011 and publishes a journal of short stories, poetry and photography each semester.
- The Tufts Canon, 2012 -- 2016; UP263.001; 0.55 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of The Tufts Canon literary journal.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - The Tufts Canon, Spring, 2012; UP263.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Volume
    1
  - The Tufts Canon, Spring, 2012; UP263.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    2
  - The Tufts Canon, Fall, 2012; UP263.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    3
  - The Tufts Canon, Spring, 2013; UP263.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    4
  - The Tufts Canon, Winter, 2014; UP263.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    5
  - The Tufts Canon, Spring, 2014; UP263.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    6
  - The Tufts Canon, Winter, 2015; UP263.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    7
  - The Tufts Canon, Spring, 2015; UP263.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - The Tufts Canon, Fall, 2015; UP263.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    9
  - Cannon, Summer, 2016; UP263..001.001.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 10)